spinfold.com 2013-12-01

# Privacy Policy | Spinfold

**Privacy Policy – Your Privacy Rights**

This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect, how we use it, how other companies may use it, and tracking technologies used to collect information. If we make any material changes to our privacy practices, we will post a revised Privacy Policy on this page. If you have any questions, please contact us by sending an email to [admin@spinfold.com](mailto:admin@spinfold.com)

**Information we collect**

**Information collected automatically:** When you visit our sites and use our apps, we automatically collect and store information about your computer or mobile device and your activities. This information includes:

  * Your computer’s IP address
  * Technical information about your computer or mobile device (such as type of device, web browser or operating system)
  * Your preferences and settings (time zone, language, etc.)
  * Your mobile device’s unique ID number
  * Your mobile device’s geographic location (specific geographic location if you’ve enabled collection of that information, or general geographic location automatically)
  * The URL of the last web page you visited before coming to one of our sites
  * The words you have looked up and results you selected
  * The ads you clicked on
  * How long you visited our sites or used our apps and which services and features you used
  * For app users, the online or offline status of Your app

**Email Address** **:**.

We use your email address only to allow you to log in to your account, send you confirmations (of your registration, etc.), and to send you messages as part of our services. You may choose to stop receiving these emails by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email.We will also use your email address to respond to your customer service inquiries.

You may request spinfold.com not disclose your personal information to third parties.You may do so by writing to us at [admin@spinfold.com](mailto:admin@spinfold.com).
